[Theme song]
[Exciting music]
[Man 1 groans in pain]
[There is a crunching sound]
[Italian]
Wait!
[Man 1 groans with difficulty]
[Man 1 screams]
[Man 1 falls]
(in advance)
[Korean]
Lawyer
Are you two okay?
Why didn't you go?
I solved it another way
(Vincenzo)
Oh, and
I forgot to feed Injagi.
[President Cho’s laughter]
[Laughs]
[President Cho sighs]
Anyway, I'm taking a step back.
(Director Kim)
Maybe Vincenzo Cassano?
Well, I don’t know anything about that.
[lighter clicks]
Let's pay some price in 5 minutes.
(Director Kim)
Bring him quickly
[intense music]
[President Cho’s angry groan]
Oh, there are so many, oh
[Fight noisily]
[Chayoung and Miri’s screams]
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
[Chayoung and Miri’s surprised moans]
(Chayoung)
What should I do, what should I do
Don't do it, don't do it
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
(Hongsik)
[Italian]
Wait!
[Tenant shouts in Italian]
[Exciting music]
[Speaks Italian]
(Director Kim)
[Korean]
Hey, what is that again?
[Fight noisily]
[Rhythmic music]
(Vincenzo)
Oh my
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Cheolwook’s spirit]
[Yeonjin’s spirit]
[Rough breathing]
[Youngho’s powerful moans]
[Toto’s spirit]
[Meaningful sound effects]
(Kiseok)
Yikes! Eek!
Eek! and!
[Punches Man 2]
[Punches Man 3]
(Seokdo)
Ouch!
[Seokdo’s spirit]
[Man 4 screams]
[There is a crunching sound]
[Seokdo’s spirit]
[Strong moan]
[breathes and then exhales]
[Sound of people breathing heavily]
[Men's groans of difficulty]
[Exciting music]
[President Cho’s heavy breathing]
(Director Kim)
I thought too easily
(Vincenzo)
boss
What is this person?
(President Cho)
He is the right-hand man of presidential candidate Park Seung-jun.
(Vincenzo)
Ah
Candidate Park Seung-jun today
My right arm will be cut off.
let's talk
I have nothing to talk about
(Director Kim)
Just create something to talk about, right?
But I'm really curious
Was gold real?
[Approaching footsteps]
[groans with difficulty]
[Director Kim falls down]
(Chayoung)
Where are you saying useless words?
[Interesting music]
(Heesu)
What were you saying when you got hit and fell down?
(Hongsik)
[Laughing]
Moller, what are you talking about?
[People laughing]
(Yeonjin)
Suddenly...
[makes a loud noise]
[Yeonjin’s elasticity]
(Joosung)
Lawyer
[People talk to each other]
(Vincenzo)
Everyone
Is everyone okay?
Oh, of course, we are all fine.
[Sigh of relief]
(Chayoung)
No, but they are all so talented.
How did you endure it?
(Toto)
There's no need to put any effort into it, yeah
And if you live without any effort,
It's a loss
(Yeonjin)
But now
These are difficult words
There was a justification for using force.
(Cheolwook)
What gave me its legitimacy
These are lawyers.
(Yeonjin)
That's right
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
(Cheolwook)
Thank you for bringing us together like this
(Heesu)
Me too, I also have to say something difficult.
'If I go alone, I'll get there quickly.
If we all go together, we'll go far'
[People cheer]
[Heesu’s laughter]
(Youngho)
In the person I admire on the school questionnaire,
I wrote 'Vincenzo Cassano'
(Kiseok)
Well done
[People laughing]
(Yeonjin)
Wow, good job
(dropping)
Thanks to the lawyers too
[Chae-shin’s pained moans]
I gained awareness of power
thank you
(Chae Shin)
wooden avalokitesvara bodhisattva
(Hongsik)
Hey, Geumga-dong Nutria!
The only skill you had was biting?
Hey, what don't you know?
That's advanced technology.
Chew, tear, taste, enjoy, 4 steps
(Hongsik)
Oh my, my goodness
nutria
[Vincenzo picks up the bottle]
Take this for me
[People laughing]
[People moan in surprise]
(Larry Kang)
Isn't it bleeding, bleeding, bleeding?
- (Larry Kang) I think I'm bleeding.
- (Seokdo) Ayu
(Kiseok)
nutria, nutria
[Savoring moans]
(Vincenzo)
boss
I keep not answering the phone
I was worried something had happened.
(President Cho)
Ah, yes
I was suddenly attacked
(Vincenzo)
Ah
sorry
(President Cho)
But lawyer
How did you move all the gold?
It would have been impossible not to notice.
[Exciting music]
[Laughs slightly]
(dropping)
Lawyer
(Vincenzo)
yes
(dropping)
One at this point
I want to ask you something.
yes please say
[surprised gasp]
(dropping)
What's down here
What is it?
(Chae Shin)
Every time I practice
Electricity keeps rising in my butt
I opened it
[Interesting music]
[Chae-shin rattles the floor]
[Chaesin’s spirit]
[The monks’ powerful moans]
(Chae Shin)
It's now, it's now, just a little bit, just a little bit
[groans with difficulty]
One, two, three!
[The monks’ powerful moans]
[surprised moan]
(Chae Shin)
Then the door to the safe...
The same thing came out
(dropping)
Every time I performed it, I said ‘aah’
It's because I'm on electricity.
[Chae-shin’s surprised gasp]
I see the light on
I think it's because of a short circuit.
[Embarrassed groan]
(Chae Shin)
here
[in a low voice]
where the gold is
Right?
[Interesting music]
Oh, is the window open?
Right?
[Laughs]
yes
[Monks’ excited moans]
[moktak sound effect]
[The enemy clears his throat]
(dropping)
Ouch!
[Monks clear their coughs]
Why to the people of Plaza
[Exciting music]
Didn't you tell me?
I'm afraid there will be trouble because of gold.
(dropping)
So I waited for the owner
[smiling slightly]
Ah, yes
[laughter]
Because now you know
I need you to help me.
[Calm piano playing]
[Exciting music]
(Chae Shin)
By the way, lawyer
How do I open this door?
Director
Now the time has come
(Vincenzo)
Let's open the secret room door tomorrow.
[Miri’s surprised gasp]
[Elasticity]
Ah, finally
By the way, lawyer
yes
(in advance)
I open it.
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
Director, I will take care of your share well.
You believe me, right?
[sigh]
(Vincenzo)
No, why...
[Vincenzo clears his throat]
[Miri’s excited breathing]
(in advance)
Sure!
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
[upbeat music]
I'll open it in one go!
(Vincenzo)
Oh, baby, yeah
- (in advance) Got it?
- (Vincenzo) Yes, I understand.
[Miri and Vincenzo cheer]
(Vincenzo)
yes
- (in advance) Okay!
- (Vincenzo) Okay
(in advance)
It's tomorrow, us!
(Vincenzo)
Let's go
- (in advance) Do you like it?
- Yeah, yeah, ah
- (in advance) Of course!
- It hurts.
(in advance)
Where are you going?
[System operating sound]
[The safe door clicks open]
[Sound effect of safe opening]
[Vincenzo’s cheers]
[cheering]
(Vincenzo)
congratulations, congratulations
Go back, go back
one, two
Give me strength, manager, give me strength
[People moan in surprise]
[People's elasticity]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[moktak sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
a little bit a day
please move the gold
[Interesting music]
[Gold bars rattle]
So where is the gold?
(Vincenzo and Joosung)
Uh…
(Joosung)
You might hear it outside
listen for a moment
yes, yes
[Interesting music]
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
[President Cho laughs]
(President Cho)
Then, together with the guillotine file...
no
The guillotine file is
I hid it in a place only I know
Ah
They didn't even teach me.
Of course for me too...
(President Cho)
yes
[Laughs slightly]
boss
I'll reveal it when the time comes.
[Soft music]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Vincenzo laughs]
(Chayoung)
Didn’t you come here because of me?
I have to take care of my Italian family too.
I solved it
in that short time
How do you solve it?
(Chayoung)
That too in Korea
80 million euros
Yes?
(Vincenzo)
Instead of leaving my family alone
We decided to give 80 million euros.
For reference, 80 million euros is in Korean won.
It will be a little over 100 billion
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
[Chayoung laughs]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
They said they would do that?
Yes, I wrote a contract and sent it to you.
(Vincenzo)
My contract has credibility in the industry.
[Chayoung takes a breath and then exhales]
If so, I'm really glad
thank you
and
I love it so much
For coming back unscathed
You look just as good today
(Chayoung)
The day we had an in-house party
Ah
The figure wearing the Bralo that I had only heard about.
It was kinda cool.
[Chayoung’s laughter]
I was happy that day too
Getting to know Bralo
meet someone
[train alarm sound]
[groans with difficulty]
[sigh]
“Gold Bar”
[Interesting music]
(Director Kim)
Oh my, Mr.
IC
[Moaning in pain]
[Director Kim’s powerful moans]
Ah!
[Chocolate falls down]
[humorous music]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Chayoung clears her throat]
[Vincenzo’s powerful moans]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Joosung)
Earlier, President Cho was there.
I can't even hug you
Now
Lawyer
(Chayoung)
It's been over 20 seconds now
(Joosung)
‘I don’t know where I am, but
There is a saying, ‘I stand out where I am’, right?
But the place where the lawyer was
There was a hole 30m in diameter.
(Vincenzo)
Ah, yes, yes, I understand.
[Strengthening]
But stop now
[Joosung’s angry moans]
The 30m diameter hole is filled, kinda.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Joosung’s angry moans]
[Vincenzo’s powerful moans]
(Chayoung)
Quickly
[Joosung’s angry moans]
Rep. Park Seung-jun should be scolded.
[Vincenzo’s responsive groan]
[Exciting music]
(Joosung)
Right?
He's a presidential candidate, so he should be scolded.
(Vincenzo)
I'm surprised
(Joosung)
Guillotine file, guillotine file
[Vincenzo laughs]
How much has Rep. Park Seung-jun suffered?
How bad are you?
(Woman 1)
Candidate Park Seung-jun’s article appeared, appeared.
(Woman 2)
Ugh, what is this, a presidential candidate?
(Woman 3)
The family was so rotten.
Is this a country?
(Director Kim)
What the hell
What are you guys?
If only Vincenzo had been dealt with from the beginning.
Ugh
I am embarrassed to say this, but
I think you acted hastily.
What is it?
You touched Vincenzo
Did you report it to the elder?
(Director Kim)
Choi Myung-hee It's nothing you need to worry about.
Vincenzo will never be taken lightly
It's not an opponent
(Myunghee)
Even though there is still clear evidence
Well, whether it's a suspicion or a story, it's solved like that.
They're all trying to make fun of us.
(Seunghyuk)
Probably during the Babel Tower Trial
There's a good chance you'll hit it right, yeah
Babel Tower related personnel video
Everything, even the ones involving the elderly
In that video, the district prosecutor
Choi Byun would have also come out.
(Director Kim)
Oh, then they're all going to get caught, right?
(Seunghyuk)
yes
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Manager
There is one way to stop the trial.
[nervous music]
Oh, instead
Senior, please do some centering.
You need to upload it
(Director Kim)
Oops, why don’t you name Chief Prosecutor Jeong?
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, Prosecutor Jeong is done with this matter.
I'm going to go into the manager's office...
(Director Kim)
Put it on quickly
Only when you have strength can you solve problems well.
(Seunghyuk)
[Laughing]
yes
(Director Kim)
Don't talk nonsense, just take it.
Yes, Chief.
(Seunghyuk)
Ah!
(Myunghee)
Congratulations in advance on your success, Manager.
[laughter]
(Unconvicted Prisoner 1)
Hey, Mr.
Are you the president of bread?
(Unconvicted Prisoner 2)
IC
(Unconvicted Prisoner 1)
If you want to live like a king, don't come in at all.
[Meaningful music]
Do you feel bad about me?
Nothing feels good
Why do I feel bad?
just
yes
A person may just be in a bad mood.
[Scream of unconvicted prisoner 1]
[There is a crunching sound]
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
[The whistle blows]
(Prison Officer 1)
Stop moving!
6723!
[There is a crunching sound]
[Scream of unconvicted prisoner 1]
(Unconvicted Prisoner 1)
Ears, ah, ears
[Unconvicted Prisoner 1 groans in pain]
[People are noisy]
[Junwoo’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
Your ears are still attached
Come to work
Come to work!
Come to work, you bastard!
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
[Chayoung’s faint moan]
[Chayoung flips through documents]
(Vincenzo)
Lawyer
I'm going to eat one of these.
It will relieve some of your fatigue.
[Savoring moans]
Of course, I have to eat this when looking at documents.
I feel like I woke up suddenly.
[The door clicks open]
[The door slams shut]
[Jusung huffs]
[Joosung groans in exasperation]
(Joosung)
Oh, really!
(Chayoung)
What's going on?
(Joosung)
It's from the Southeastern District Court.
Please read it
[Joosung takes a breath and then exhales]
[Meaningful music]
(Chayoung)
‘Regarding the above incident’
‘This trial related to Babel Tower’
'Unconfirmed by the media
‘Provocative reports’
'Content of Internet jokes, etc.
'When inferring'
'For specific candidates for the next presidential election,
'With black propaganda'
'There is a possibility of abuse.
'It is judged to be high'
‘Accordingly, the Southeastern District Court of the Ministry of Justice and the National Election Commission’
'After consultation, this trial
'Decided to postpone until after the election'
‘This is an emergency notification’
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
Rep. Park Seung-jun
Looks like you used some force.
(Joosung)
This is perfect, huh? Really, wow, this
[Joosung sighs]
No, like this
Does it come off as mean and mean?
(Vincenzo)
From over there, mean and mean
Because it came out
We should do the same
[Chayoung and Joosung sigh]
(Chayoung)
How?
It's already in the mood to go to trial.
[Vincenzo’s groan of denial]
We have a magic lamp
Guillotine?
[Snaps fingers]
[Exciting music]
[Mouse click sound]
[Chayoung sighs]
- (Vincenzo) Yes
- (Joosung) From here onwards
- Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office, yes.
- (Joosung) Yes, Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office
(Vincenzo)
It's there
[Mouse click sound]
Oh my, this
[Chayoung hits the desk]
(Chayoung)
IC
[Chayoung sighs]
In the lawyer's anonymous room
This is information that was just uploaded.
This trial is suspended
It was carried out under the leadership of Prosecutor Jeong In-guk.
What makes me more upset is
You have finally become a manager.
[Jusung laughs]
Such a traitor
In commemoration of being buried
Let me give you a gift, okay?
[lighter clicks]
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
It doesn't work
[Joosung laughs]
(Vincenzo)
The lawyer was right.
This whole country is doing mafia work.
Bafia, Morfia
mafia, sepia, hakpia
[Vincenzo laughs]
Why is there so much?
If you are competent, you can be corrupt.
This is Korea’s representative trend.
[Groans of approval]
No, but
Can one be competent if one is corrupt?
If you are corrupt, you are only good for yourself.
Becoming incompetent to others
Ah
I completely acknowledge that statement from the villain's point of view.
[Chayoung laughs]
If you finish everything as planned and leave
You won't be able to return to Korea easily, right?
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
Still, to me, Vincenzo Cassano is
I won't be left like a stuffed animal
Lawyer
(Vincenzo)
I do nothing but business
Have you ever made a promise to someone?
Never
But I promise
I will definitely come back
(Yun Byeon)
'About the above trial
'Further discussion is needed'
[Meaningful music]
‘After discussion, it was renegotiated like this.’
‘The above trial is about the next presidential election’
'It can be abused as black propaganda.
'The possibility is slim'
'Due to the development of Babel Tower,
'The pain of the accusers is greater'
'I want the trial to proceed as usual.
'Notify'
sorry
(Myunghee)
Manager Jeong
You said you were confident, but what is this?
I was playing around with the guillotine file over there.
What should I do?
I should have expected that much!
Then, with a lawyer who is good at predicting things,
The district prosecutor will solve it.
What?
hey!
[sigh]
[Myunghee’s angry groan]
[Rough breathing]
(Seunghyuk)
It's so cold
Oh, I'm so cold, huh?
- (Seunghyuk) Oh, it’s so cold.
- (Judge Heo) Let’s go
(Seunghyuk)
Who is it?
(Judge Heo)
Judge Heo
(Seunghyuk)
Huh? Ah, Judge Heo, ah, brother!
[Laugh together]
Brother, brother, brother says so
My brother is in charge of this game, huh?
Final defender, huh?
[Judge Heo’s elasticity]
Sweeper, okay?
- (Judge Heo) Sweeper?
- (Seunghyuk) Uh, so
Man, focus, just focus!
(Seunghyuk)
Oh my, it's a surprise, sure, Mr.
Oh my, I almost hit you, Mr.
[Judge Heo laughs]
Okay, so
No matter how the situation unfolds
[Ancient music]
My brother last
I have to stop it.
Okay, come on in.
Chief Prosecutor
[Laugh together]
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, oh, take it easy, take it easy
I'm going, I'm going
(Judge Heo)
Ah, this way, this way.
(Seunghyuk)
Wow, the car is the same
[Seunghyuk and Judge Heo laugh]
- (Judge Heo) Oh my gosh
- (Seunghyuk) You know
[Seunghyuk and Judge Heo laugh]
(Seunghyuk)
Baby, don't do that, baby, bro, don't do that.
Oh, take it easy, take it easy
Baby, I'm so sleepy
I'm going to sleep now, I'm going
[Seunghyuk’s powerful moans]
[Judge Heo laughs]
(Seunghyuk)
hello
(Judge Heo)
nice
(Seunghyuk)
hello
(Judge Heo)
You sound like a sweeper, sir.
I know how to set off bombs.
Oh my, shit, shit.
Open the door!
Eight
Tsk
[Judge Heo’s disapproving groan]
let's go quickly
[Exciting music]
[Gear operation sound]
[surprised moan]
(Judge Heo)
Hey
Why aren't you going home?
[Unfasten the seat belt]
[surprised moan]
Everything, you
Vincennes Casanova?
[surprised moan]
(Vincenzo)
get down
[Car door opens]
(Judge Heo)
What are we going to do now?
You know that story?
I don't know
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
Cambyses, king of ancient Persia
A harsh punishment was imposed on the corrupt judge.
Skinned a corrupt judge alive
Oh my gosh
And then you know what happened?
I don't know
(Vincenzo)
The corrupt judge's son was also a judge.
When the son judges
father's skin
I used it as a chair mat.
[trembling moan]
So that we can come to our senses and have a fair trial.
What do you mean?
[Loads the gun]
(Vincenzo)
If only it were like before
You too are someone's
What I'm saying is that it would have become a chair mat.
Ouch
(Vincenzo)
Chairman Jang Han-seok's trial, you are the judge, right?
yes
As we have done so far
Please listen to Jang Han-seok a lot.
So that it can come out as quickly as possible
Even if you try to get it out as quickly as possible
It's 2 months
Then never extend the detention.
If you disobey me
This time it won't end with a wasp.
[Judge Heo’s trembling breathing]
goodbye
(Vincenzo)
The law is like a spider's web
And durability is limited.
These strong wasps bite and run away
Weak flies get trapped and die.
But the flies gathered here
join forces together
Wasp, biting all the spider webs
Today will be the day to feel it
Watch carefully
What happens to the wasps?
Let's all go together
(Joosung)
Let's go
(Hongsik)
one, two, three
(together)
Let's go!
[Rhythmic music]
(Myunghee)
Where are the attachments here?
Attached material, first…
I said it ten times.
ten times, ten times
(lawyer)
Chairman
please come this way
[Lawyer's awkward laugh]
[Awkward laughter]
(Chinese book)
yes
sit, sit
[The door slams shut]
Sit down, what are you doing in the hallowed court?
Oh…
yes
[The door clicks open]
(Inspector)
Your Honor is coming in.
Everyone wake up
[Puts down the documents]
[Clears cough]
(Inspector)
Everyone please sit down
[Meaningful music]
(Judge Heo)
From now on
2021Gahap30184
Due to Babel Group’s illegal activities
Trial on Geumga Plaza’s claim for damages
Let's get started
Let's start by examining the plaintiff's witnesses.
Examine the plaintiff's attorney's witness
(Chayoung)
Witness Vincenzo Cassano
please come forward
[People cheering]
[Clears cough]
(Chinese book)
head here
Fighting
oath
Ah, honorable judge.
(Judge Heo)
yes
Dear Judge,
I am Babel Group
Why did you do this illegal act?
I'm going to testify
my testimony
I will replace it with video evidence.
(Myunghee)
Your Honor
[Meaningful music]
This video is
It has nothing to do with this trial...
(Judge Heo)
Because it may contain important information
I will watch the video and decide.
Please sit down
Please play the data.
[Video sound plays]
(Cheolwook)
Oh my, what is this?
Oh my, huh?
(Sunam)
What is that, is that, a golden toad? gold!
(Cheolwook)
No way, a
[People are upset]
Golden toad?
[sigh]
[groans with difficulty]
But why is it a mosaic?
[People in the video are noisy]
(Myunghee)
Why can't we just come out?
why…
[Meaningful music]
(Inspector)
please be quiet
Please be quiet!
(Prosecutor Jeong)
don't come
[heavy music]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s groans of difficulty]
[Italian]
Nice to meet you, friend.
[Prosecutor Jeong chuckles]
[Korean]
Did I warn you?
Do whatever you want
If you get to enjoy everything
I'll kill you then
[Prosecutor Jeong’s groans of difficulty]
[Prosecutor Jeong chuckles]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s heavy breathing]
Was it like that?
[laughter]
I don't remember much
But he even got a manager
They even tried to stop the trial.
(Vincenzo)
Anyway congratulations
He ignored my warning and chose death.
[Prosecutor Jeong’s heavy breathing]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
yes
Try killing the chief prosecutor inside the court.
Don't be bluff
to me in two days
Show some humility just once
(Vincenzo)
I'll save your life
It's my rare tolerance
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Just a mafia bastard
Republic of Korea Chief Prosecutor
You shouldn't play with it
[Laughs slightly]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s groans of difficulty]
[Prosecutor Jeong is cackling]
not playing with it
I'm giving you a chance to not regret it
[Prosecutor Jeong chuckles]
[Rough breathing]
[The door slams shut]
[train alarm sound]
[Seunghyuk sighs]
(Seunghyuk)
Wow, I feel really uncomfortable, Mr.
[Seunghyuk’s painful moans]
No, why, why are we the only mosaics, why?
Why?
They say it's because the porridge is soggy.
It's hard to kill in a prison cell.
(Seunghyuk)
I know, I know, I know that.
[Seunghyuk’s refreshing groan]
No, but
We're all about to be slaughtered
What, are you this carefree?
Well, then
Should I go to Gangnam University and cry?
a way to get out
You need to think about it.
(Myunghee)
Now, find your way to live, Chief Prosecutor.
Yes?
[Myunghee puts down the bottle]
This is our farewell note
[Meaningful music]
[train alarm sound]
[Myunghee’s refreshing groan]
(Myunghee)
Nice place
You seduced me in the first place
No, what can I say...
(Seunghyuk)
Oh my, really
In times like this, we
We have to come together
Fish oil, indeed
It's so damn hard to get together
(Myunghee)
Because it wasn’t enough to seduce Jang Han-seo to ask me to live with him.
I rub my hands against Rep. Park Seung-jun.
The bastard who became the chief prosecutor
Rip the mouth open, ma, tsk
If I say this
I'm really sad, huh?
Honestly, senior
Because of who, because of who
Living like this, enjoying wealth and fame
(Seunghyuk)
Look at this, look at this, look at the stains that have improved
Don’t you remember the old days?
Oh my, it's me
Thanks, okay.
You snake-like bastard.
Snake?
(Myunghee)
Let’s live your life one more time
Chairman Jang Han-seok
You're harming me, right?
I sprained my hand, did you know?
[Elasticity]
ate well
[Calm music]
(Seunghyuk)
Yeah, uh, go your separate ways, go
Let’s go, Choi Myung-hee!
Later, later, huh?
Don't pray in front of me
I am the district prosecutor! I, Mr.
(Anchor on TV)
The impact of this Babel Tower Gate is huge.
Prosecutors, police, National Assembly, media
Injustice and corruption throughout local organizations
Citizens are shocked
Also, the Babel Tower site
carried out in the process of illegal acquisition
About Geumga Plaza tenants
Indiscriminate assault and attempted murder
It's causing a stir
Due to licensing irregularities and illegal activities
About Geumga Plaza
Babel Group’s ownership is
We are planning to begin the registration process for cancellation.
[People cheering]
[Music that heightens the mood]
Uh, stop producing the RDU-90 first.
(Chinese book)
Yes, the import of raw materials has also been canceled.
No, it's okay.
It's okay, just follow my instructions.
Oh, good work
Oh, I'm sorry, I really am.
I have a lot of things to deal with urgently.
Wow
really
[Elasticity]
You really look like the president now.
I'm so proud, really
What else am I proud of, not even my mom?
[Laughing]
A
[Laugh together]
(Chinese book)
Oh, but hey, what is your business?
Ah, that
Did you see the video from yesterday’s trial?
(Seunghyuk)
Only we are a mosaic
[Laughs]
That's it
They're doing it to kill us.
So, the chairman and I
Let's join forces again...
No, I'm joining forces with Vincenzo.
Yes?
[humorous music]
With the Chief Prosecutor and Vincenzo
Different grades
I'm going to do it with Go Soo.
No, no matter what
In this way...
(Seunghyuk)
Vincenzo at first
Well, who let you meet?
I made it possible for you to meet me!
- That's right.
- (Seunghyuk) Oh
That's right, that's right, ah!
(Chinese book)
Oh, sorry, I really forgot.
Oh, I really appreciate it.
- (Seunghyuk) Yes
- (Hanseo) Thank you so much, really.
It can be done, it can be done
[Elasticity of Hanseo]
(Seunghyuk)
It's okay
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
But now the district prosecutor's job is
Take care of it
What do you do? Let's do it together
[Hanseo mutters]
(Seunghyuk)
Chairman
[Strong moan]
Uh, the chief prosecutor is leaving.
Hurry up, you're in a hurry
I'm not in a hurry?
Can you please join me?
[Meaningful music]
[Approaching footsteps]
(Prison Guard 2)
6723 visit
[Junwoo sighs]
[The door slams shut]
Why?
(Junwoo)
Are you here to pick up some medicine?
You won?
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
If you just listen to it
I'm afraid you won't be able to feel it
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Meaningful music]
I'm sorry for going in without permission.
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
[gunshot]
[Music that heightens the mood]
(Vincenzo)
Still, I'm so glad
It's not a real building
[laughter]
The Tower of Babel has fallen
You know what's left, right?
[Meaningful music]
[sigh]
[Junwoo laughs]
[Speaks Italian]
Now I'm a hungry cat
(Junwoo)
yes
Try catching it somewhere
From head to tail
When you come out
After a grand dinner
When I get out of here
It won't be Chairman Jang Han-seok.
(Vincenzo)
uh
Yeah?
I'm going to go out as my younger self
A monster that didn't care about anything
Not Babel’s Chairman Jang Han-seok
You're just dealing with me
[Elasticity]
Sounds interesting, yeah
You know my past well, right?
(Junwoo)
To my friends when I was young
what did you do
maybe your watch
You'll be in my dressing room
(Vincenzo)
whatever you like
I have great experience in leading youth.
[The door clicks open]
[The door slams shut]
(Seunghyuk)
Manager Jeong
I have one urgent favor to ask of you.
[Sighing]
me
Just let me stay in the detention center for three months.
[Interesting music]
Yes?
You probably know why I do this
That Vincen...
(Seunghyuk)
So
I made a picture and sent it to the detention center.
Just three months
In the meantime, if Vincenzo dies,
Take me out right away
No, but how can the Chief Prosecutor...
Just do it, do it, just do it
(Seunghyuk)
If you do this
Including Chairman Jang, huh?
The clients of our idols
Information comparable to that guillotine file
I give everything to Manager Jeong.
In this case, Director Jeong, just go up there.
Just hit it hard and go up.
Okay? uh?
[Awkward laughter]
Oh, do it
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Elasticity of Hanseo]
[Hanseo takes a breath]
(Vincenzo)
Is it pizza?
(Chinese book)
Yes, Korean Pizza
[Hanseo gulps down]
Ah, bro
When it's all over, really
Are you leaving Korea?
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
Ah
Can't I go?
(Chinese book)
I am Babel Group’s legal team.
I'll give you a position as an advisor.
Director Daewoo-ro
That's enough
No, then you can just go whenever you want, okay?
Without a sound or rumor
You can't just disappear
(Chinese book)
Huh? After watching the mafia movie
That's just what they said
(Vincenzo)
Mafia farewell party
There are many times when I leave after a week.
(Chinese book)
really? I need to do it for a week, a week, really.
[Pours a drink]
(Vincenzo)
Ah
[Vincenzo puts down the bottle]
There was no contact from Jang Han-seok?
Yes, it's very quiet.
If you push this and that
You will get the right sentence, right?
I don't know that yet
So it could come out in two months?
[Lonely music]
(Vincenzo)
you
I'm avoiding abroad for the time being.
Even if it's just for a few months
Huh?
Jang Han-seok
When it comes out, they'll try to get rid of you first.
I will recommend a safe place
[takes a breath]
It's okay, bro.
In the first place
I started by sacrificing my life.
And I made a promise to my brother.
You can keep your promise with me later.
think again
[sigh]
(Chinese book)
Um…
No, I want to fight.
I have also deployed 20 bodyguards.
I don't get offended easily
[sigh]
and
Definitely for me
We have a brother, Bin.
He knows everything and blocks everything, huh?
Hitting everyone
Bro, ah, really
Why are you so cool?
(Vincenzo)
Hey, hey, that's soy sauce, soy sauce
Soy sauce, soy sauce, soy sauce, soy sauce
Baby, ya
[Puts the bowl down]
(Chinese book)
Let me tell you a little bit, a little bit
[Hanseo taps the table]
[Meaningful music]
(Myunghee)
what should i do
Can we get Chairman Jang out?
[Atmospheric music plays]
(Chayoung)
Lawyer
If Jang Han-seok comes out this time,
Are we going as planned without any changes?
Lawyer
(Vincenzo)
Finishing Jang Han-seok’s side
You can really skip the lawyer this time.
I was a villain until now
After this is over
You really become the devil.
I want to protect the lawyer's line.
[sigh]
What we've done so far
[Calm music]
Honestly, it was so cruel that I couldn't bear it.
(Chayoung)
But why am I following the lawyer’s wishes?
Do you know if you followed it?
People like Jang Han-seok should be punished.
There is no best law
There is no second best law.
So I followed the lawyer’s lesser evil.
Because it felt right.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Chayoung laughs]
Look at this person
Why?
They say they all released Director Jeong In-guk.
(Chayoung)
It was in the video at Jang Han-seok’s house.
Everyone.
In the end, you refused my last indulgence.
[Clinks the glass]
[Laughs]
(Director Kim)
Make things like this
What are you asking for help with?
I can really finish it all this time
Vincenzo and Guillotine Files too.
(Director Kim)
Tsk, that's enough
Vincenzo and the guillotine file, tsk
We'll take care of it.
That's
No
Aren’t you in the middle of an election campaign?
While dealing with Vincenzo, things went wrong.
Try at least a spark
It'll be another scandal
[sigh]
For the comfort of the elderly
Please let me cancel the decision.
How are you going to cancel the decision?
Chairman Jang Han-seok
Please help me come out somehow.
(Director Kim)
Chairman Jang is the biggest problem right now.
He is the most difficult person to bring out.
Senior
[Lawyer's sigh]
(Myunghee)
Give me what I ordered
[The lawyer speaks]
(Myunghee)
Since I was a prosecutor
for my own benefit
Evidence that Babel was instigated and pressured
I made it all
No judge or prosecutor can complain.
in the evidence
Chairman Jang Han-seok
It's just my scarecrow
No, then
Choi Myung-hee, you?
yes
I turned everything upside down
I'll go in
Putting an end to the Babel Tower scandal
Who will face Vincenzo?
There is only Chairman Jang Han-seok.
[Rhythmic music plays]
(Inspector 1)
Yeah
[Prosecutor Jeong’s laughter]
Manager!
Congratulations 10 and 100 times on your success!
[People cheering]
(Inspector 2)
Congratulations!
[Prosecutor 1’s laughter]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
us
They are prosecutors of the Republic of Korea.
Never bend or lose, especially
These chaebol bastards
If it breaks, it will definitely be crushed.
Do you understand?
(people)
Yes!
Now, raise your glass.
For the Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office!
(people)
For!
(Inspector 1)
For one more time!
(Inspector 3)
Congratulations!
(Inspector 2)
Manager, congratulations!
(Inspector 4)
Congratulations!
[People cheering]
[A siren rings in the distance]
[laughter]
[sigh]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s laughter]
[nervous music]
you
Vincenzo
[Prosecutor Jeong’s surprised groan]
[A commotion is heard]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Hey!
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s groans of difficulty]
[surprised gasp]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s heavy breathing]
[Meaningful music]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s trembling breathing]
you bastard
My generosity comes at a price.
I won't accept it
Shut up, you mafia bastard!
[Prosecutor Jeong’s trembling breathing]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
This criminal bastard has a lot of arrogance, Mr.
Even if I'm a criminal
I know what I did wrong
Why don't you know?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
I didn't do anything wrong
according to principle
I am a person who lives according to order.
Okay
If you don't know what's wrong
I'll make sure you don't go wrong
[Italian]
If there is no life
There is nothing wrong!
[People talk]
[Prosecutor Jeong falls]
[Car warning sound]
(Man 5)
[Korean]
Hey, aren't you human?
(Man 6)
Huh?
Hey, what is it?
[elegant music]
[Elegant music plays]
(Vincenzo)
one is over
Now other things too
We have to sort things out one by one.
me
And for Attorney Hong Cha-young
(Myunghee)
The evidence is already complete
I made it
There was no need to go that far.
(Myunghee)
It's okay
Well, just pretend to be embarrassed
I have to drag them all in.
No regrets
After going out and taking care of yourselves,
You can take me out.
(Junwoo)
If he comes out, the next vice president of Babel Group will be
It's Choi Byeon.
thank you
(Myunghee)
You told me to watch
Vice Chairman Jang Han-seo
Very definitely towards Vincenzo
I think it passed
[laughter]
[Meaningful music]
Be sure to show it off
[Junwoo sighs]
(Myunghee)
Did you hear about Prosecutor Jeong’s suicide?
(Junwoo)
yes
After the promotion party is over, I kill it.
It's so cruel
Vincenzo is definitely
Looks like it's starting
I have one condition if I go out.
ASAP
I'm leaving without anyone knowing
without anyone knowing
alone
[Exciting music plays]
One, two, one, two, two
(Myunghee)
One, two, three, four
One, two
One, two, three, four, yeah
[Myeonghee’s Chuimsae]
One, two, three, four
(Investigator)
Myunghee Choi
Came from the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
Charged with abetting and abetting tax evasion and abetting murder
I'm under urgent arrest.
(Myunghee)
Just 2 minutes
It's over in 2 minutes
Miranda notice is over.
[Strong moan]
Choi Myung-hee was captured?
(Joosung)
Yes, what is the crime?
It was enormous.
I guess a subordinate lawyer stabbed me in the stomach.
Then it's 100% positive.
(Chayoung)
Well, in the meantime, Choi Myung-hee
How much did they fry it?
If you can't protect your family
That's what happens in the end
(Myunghee)
♪ Lascia ch'io pianga ♪
[Meaningful music]
♪ La dura sorte ♪
♪ E che so spiri ♪
♪ La liberta ♪
[Chayoung clears her throat]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Soft music]
(Vincenzo)
Where are you going?
(Chayoung)
Training center alumni meeting, why?
(Vincenzo)
Ah
No, let's go somewhere with me.
I knew it would be like that
(Chayoung)
Oh, look at this wayward sense
(Vincenzo)
But why do you go to the training center’s alumni meeting?
You said things weren't going well at the time.
(Chayoung)
I'm not going because I want to go.
They're going to monitor whether I'm chewing or not.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, what time does it end?
(Chayoung)
You'll know when it's over, right?
But I have to go up to go home.
yes, i know
Well, I have somewhere to go too.
With nowhere to go
(Chayoung)
I'm going, grab some food and eat.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, what time does it end?
(Chayoung)
I don't know
(Vincenzo)
Do you drink alcohol?
(Chayoung)
A lot
(Vincenzo)
What, are you picking me up?
no!
Is this a gathering of female classmates?
(Chayoung)
[Affectionately]
There are also men
[sigh]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Call connection tone]
Ah, yes, monk.
Yes, Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva
Oh, what about meals?
Oh, fasting
(Vincenzo)
No, yes, oh, yes, sorry, yes
Yes, please come in.
Yes, Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva
[sigh]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[nervous music]
[tire rubbing sound]
[Car door clicks]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Uh, Mikyung.
I'm in the parking lot, uh
Hyewon and Hyeji came too, right?
Yeah
Okay, I'll be right there.
[laughter]
[Music that heightens tension]
[tire rubbing sound]
[Chayoung’s scream]
[sigh]
[A knocking sound is heard]
What, Secretary Kim hasn’t gotten off work yet?
Secretary Kim
[nervous music]
[surprised moan]
To surprise my brother
I came out quietly
[Junwoo laughs]
(Junwoo)
What do you do if you have a lot of bodyguards?
I gave them money, so I took it and left.
[Hanseo’s trembling breathing]
You clumsy traitor
not betrayal
[heavy music]
I was just trying to normalize Babel
[laughter]
[surprised gasp]
I brought your gun
I don't have anywhere to get a gun right now.
(Chinese book)
yes
That's right
I really can't keep you alive now
I understand, right?
[Music that heightens tension]
[shaking breathing]
yes
I'll end up like my father anyway
It was fate
I will accept it
[laughter]
[Call connection tone]
[Guidance voice]
Your phone is off
You will be connected to voicemail
After the beep sound, a call fee is charged...
[sigh]
[Call end sound]
True
[Picks up the glass]
[sigh]
[Puts down the bottle]
[laughter]
[nervous music]
[Door rattles]
[A knocking sound is heard]
[Loads the gun]
[Tense sound effect]
[Meaningful music]
[nervous music]
[Dark sound effect]
[Hanseo’s groans of difficulty]
(Chayoung)
Jang Han-seok
[surprised gasp]
Now
[Rough breathing]
Are you okay?
[groans with difficulty]
[Approaching footsteps]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[shaking breathing]
[sigh]
I thought it was impossible, but they kidnapped me too?
Isn’t this really a cheap villain?
Where are the expensive and cheap villains?
(Junwoo)
They're all just the same villains
No matter how many times I think about it
you are not a human
[dark music]
(Junwoo)
How much I love my senior
If you love, you are human.
Kidnapping someone you love
It's not love, it's crime
You crazy bastard
Sorry, senior
(Junwoo)
My principles come before love
(Chayoung)
Your principles?
Kill everyone you don’t like?
Hey
It's a real fucking festival
[Chayoung laughs]
Han Seok-ah
If you were born in this world from the beginning
That's not possible, you bastard
[Painful elasticity]
(Junwoo)
Those words are so hurtful?
‘You shouldn’t be born into this world’
Right, Hanseo?
[Hanseo’s trembling breathing]
[Chayoung sighs]
kill me quickly
Don’t call Attorney Vincenzo for nothing.
Then it won't work
Why did I bring my senior?
(Chayoung)
Hey!
Instead of making me a nuisance, kill me!
[Meaningful music]
[Call connection tone]
[Chayoung’s heavy breathing]
[cell phone ringing sound]
Where is Attorney Hong Cha-young?
(Junwoo)
Before that, I should ask how you are doing.
I came out of the detention center
I'm not interested
(Vincenzo)
Where is Attorney Hong?
Come quickly to where I am
(Junwoo)
Because Hong Cha-young is alive
I understand even if it’s a bit rude.
Detention center friends say
When you make someone who owes money come to you
They said this works best
Attorney Hong Cha-young, if something goes wrong, you die.
If it doesn't come quickly, it's really wrong.
[Call end sound]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Vincenzo’s heavy breathing]
[shaking breathing]
blood on necklace
Are you surprised?
That's pig blood
I tried it once too
It's lower than I thought
(Vincenzo)
To my younger brother
If that wasn't enough, they even kidnapped the woman.
[Vincenzo laughs]
(Junwoo)
A rat that might be caught and eaten
What would you cover?
If I kill everyone here
Do you think you can survive?
[Elasticity]
What's always behind the mafia?
think well
No matter what you do, you're going to die
Even if I die
I want to see you die first
[Junwoo sighs]
[Hanseo’s trembling breathing]
Pick it up, Jang Han-seo.
Pick it up!
[gunshot]
[Frightened groan]
[Rough breathing]
(Junwoo)
Chairman Jang Han-seo
If you kill Vincenzo with that,
I'll save you
Yes?
(Junwoo)
If you do as I say, of course I will save your life.
Babel Pharmaceutical and Babel Chemical will give you everything.
(Chayoung)
Hey, you crazy bastard!
[Rough breathing]
You are a real money bastard, you are a real money bastard!
[groans with difficulty]
[nervous music]
(Junwoo)
Senior, be quiet.
[Chayoung’s heavy breathing]
If you keep talking, is it really going to kill you?
[Chayoung laughs]
Then really kill me
Stop playing with your lame jokes
[Junwoo takes a breath]
[shaking breathing]
[Meaningful music]
Do as you're told
If you kill Vincenzo
Are you really going to save me?
Then
you are my younger brother
[shaking breathing]
I'm sorry
Attorney Vincenzo
It's okay
It's a choice you can't help but make
yes
I'm trying to make a choice without regrets
[Music that heightens the mood]
[gunshot]
(Junwoo)
Die!
[Chayoung’s surprised gasp]
[Hanseo’s angry groan]
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
Please stop!
[Hanseo’s groans of difficulty]
[gunshot]
[Meaningful music]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
[Chayoung’s groans of difficulty]
[Heavy breathing]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[shaking breathing]
[Heavy breathing]
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won